how'd I get this
everybody wants
[Music]
boy coming in strong
good what's going on YouTube this is Rob
beast from Rhode Island tattoo company
in Johnston Rhode Island and today we're
gonna be doing a machine review on my
everyday machine versus a hard life
gambler comes in gold chrome and black
pearl so the reason I like this machine
so much obviously its small it's pretty
lightweight and only weighs five point
two ounces it's about 3.7 inches long
and it comes in 3.5 stroke so the
biggest advantage I like about this
machine obviously other than it hits my
hand is that it's pretty light it hits
just like a coil obviously in the
brewery but it's just very consistent I
know a lot of people out there and
checking this machine out not really
sure about it so we figured we'd go over
a few things self-explanatory very easy
grip comes off as you can see it's very
easy they actually are making
disposables that are going to be coming
out I think within the next month it's a
pretty lightweight machine has the same
kind of style as the hawk pens or any of
the other pens of the grip comes right
off and goes on the motor is pretty
self-explanatory
it's a patent-pending motor that they
came up with they also have the nucleus
battery that goes with it the battery is
awesome because literally you could plug
and play you just basically plug it into
the top insert your cartridge whatever
brand you use and go to town you just
basically wrap up the whole machine this
whole combo has basically changed
tattooing as it is because there's no
more wires there's no more you know
destroying RCA cables because you
accidentally rolled over it there's no
power supply there's no looking for
power recently we had a power outage at
the shop and I didn't know if I was
actually going to be able to tattoo
because somebody had had a telephone
pole and it knocked out all the electric
so from that point I mean I already had
my batteries fully charged so the
batteries basically last anyway
between six to eight hours depending on
how you're tattooing this machine is
definitely a game changer by any means I
mean when I go to tattoo this is the
Machine I pick up and I've tried every
machine out there from the axis Valhalla
to I even just recently just received a
rook quill pen awesome machine but I
keep going back to my daily driver which
is the hard life because of the fact
that the machine can push anything from
a three-line are all the way up to 27
mag no problems it's very easily
adjustable if fixing your hand it's
small its compact like I said it weighs
nothing
the battery is an awesome future
basically the power supply in your hand
comes in a pack of two so I mean
literally I can if I need it to when I
do the hardest use one I got both colors
so far I don't have the black one yet
we'll see what goes on
maybe I'll get it but I pretty much use
this guy every single day it can pack
color it can line everything like I said
from a three liner all the way up to a
14 round if you needed to line something
it this is an amazing machine I can't
say honestly much about it that isn't
already known there's very rarely any
vibration to it there's no noise to it
like this is without a cartridge and
that's running like I said there's
really no noise to it the battery is
awesome you could just go about
tattooing I have no issues with it
you know you turn it off shove it on st.
button and you can adjust on how fast
you want to go goes all the way up to 26
on the numbers I've run it at 26 all the
way down to 20 I don't usually go to
much lower than that unless I'm doing
very very light black and gray but like
I said these guys are really good they
stick behind what they build it's
artists made for artists so they
understand you know the needs for an
artist the batteries will work with any
other machine but obviously work best
with the gamblers the batteries you get
two for 350 I believe it is and the
machine the price depends on the color
you want the Chrome
there's obviously the first machine that
they sold and now they have the gold and
they have black pearl black pearl and
the gold I believe our $100 more
but they'll well worth it this super
smooth shading is very very easy call
grace uses them Dani Weber a couple
other guys I know that I've seen I've
been using this machine and the custom
service is great the guys that are real
quick getting off the machines to
everybody they'll answer any questions
it doesn't matter what social media hit
them up on Instagram Facebook whatever
they're really quick and getting back to
you a very impressed with the machine
like I said I left a machine company
that I was already sponsored with so
it's not a biased opinion it's my
personal opinion I left the company just
because I just felt like I wanted to try
other things and honestly this is the
best machine that I've been using thus
far that's why it is my daily driver so
check them out man hard life rotaries
dot-com like I said awesome awesome
machines super light you can push
anything it doesn't matter they can run
super slow I know some people will still
opt out to use the power supply it's
awesome
a machine runs super super low so you
can get a really nice smooth black and
grey hit like I said it runs just like a
coil but it's a rotary so you won't be
disappointed check them out on life
rotor is calm this is Rob beast from
Rhode Island tattoo company thanks for
watching